Alright, now that you're good and inspired.
Ready to get designing, itching to draw.
You got ideas circling in your head.
The first thing you need to do is have a Croquis, which is the basic figure to design upon.
It comes from the French word to sketch.
So I'm sure you've probably never heard it.
If you have, more power to you 'cause I hadn't.
This is the word.
Visual.
And the basic figure when it's finished without color is going to look like this.
This is one of mine from awhile back.
This is my design.
This is the basic figure.
It's a skinny stretched out version of a human.
It's very important before you start designing any collection and every collection to have a stable of these croquis where you can just have them in a sketch pad and then you can just draw and sketch little designs on each one.
You don't want to have to spend your whole time doing the figuring getting it right which is why we're going to work on that right now.
And I'll show you how to have a perfect figure in which to design your designs upon.